Inventory of the Vertical (Subject) Files, 1831 - [ongoing]
Vertical (Subject) Files, 1831 - [ongoing]
Special Collections & Archives, Wesleyan University
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)
1000-176
78
39
The Vertical Files Collection has been gathered the Wesleyan University Archives to provide general information about Wesleyan University topics.
The Vertical Files Collection is comprised of materials about Wesleyan University. The materials, which include clippings, memos, fliers, programs, correspondence, and photographs, form the basis of this reference collection. Within the Vertical Files, materials are organized into groups, and within these groups, the folders are arranged alphabetically.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
No restrictions. Material may be consulted in the Special Collections & Archives Reading Room. Due to limited staff, we cannot photocopy or scan entire folders. Reference questions should be sent to sca @wesleyan.edu
Acquisitions Information
Collected by the University Archives.
Historical Note
The Vertical Files Collection has been gathered by the Wesleyan University Archives to provide general information about Wesleyan University topics.
Collection Overview
The Vertical Files Collection is comprised of materials about Wesleyan University. The materials, which include clippings, memos, fliers, programs, correspondence, and photographs, form the basis of this reference collection. Within the Vertical Files, materials are organized into groups, and within these groups, the folders are arranged alphabetically.
Online Catalog Headings
These and related materials may be found under the following headings in online catalogs.
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--History.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Faculty.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Students.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Alumni and alumnae.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Administration.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Buildings.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Sports.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Admission.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Curricula.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Presidents.
Detailed Description of the Collection
- General Subjects
  - Academic regalia
  - Accreditation
  - Activism
  - Affirmative action
  - Africans/African-Americans, 19th Century
  - Africans/African-Americans, 1900-1960
  - Africans/African-Americans, 1960-1979
  - Africans/African-Americans, 1980-1989
  - Africans/African-Americans, 1990-present
  - AIDS
  - Alcohol
  - Animals
  - Antitrust investigation, 1989-1993
  - Asia, interest in, relationship with
  - Asians/Asian-Americans
  - Awareness Month
  - Baldwin Medal/Lectures
  - Black History Month
  - Blood drive
  - Boon Tan
  - Breath holding record
  - Buddhism
  - Buttstock
  - Calendar
  - Campus speakers
  - Canada/Canadians
  - Canes, class
  - Cannon Scrap/Douglas Cannon
  - Cardinal (Mascot)
  - Chalkings
  - Charters and by-laws, to 1960
  - Charters and by-laws, 1960-
  - Citations from other institutions
  - Class albums
  - Coat-of-arms
  - Co-education, proposed
  - Co-education, second phase, 1960-
  - Colors, college
  - Commencement, general
  - Commencement addresses
  - Commencement illustration
  - Commencement, marshal's notice
  - Computers, general
  - Convocation
  - Crimes
  - Crimes, May 6, 2009, event
  - Degrees, honorary
  - Degrees, honorary (citations), to 1960
  - Degrees, M.A., M.S., and Ph. D.
  - Degrees, M.A. ad eundem gradum (MAAE)
  - Diplomas
  - Diplomat-in-residence
  - Disabilities
  - Disasters/Disaster relief
  - Diversity
  - Drugs
  - Duke Day, Uncle
  - Employment, student
  - Endowment funds and benefactors
  - Energy
  - Environmental issues
  - Finances
  - Flag scraps
  - Food/Dining halls/Restaurants
  - Foreign students
  - Forum
  - Fountain Street incident, 2008
  - France, relations with
  - Fundraising
  - Germany, relations with
  - Ghosts
  - Governance
  - Handicapped/Special needs students
  - Health/Medical
  - History, General
  - History, Bibliography
  - History, Comparative statistics
  - History, Long range plans
  - History, popular images, to 1979
  - History, popular images, 1980-
  - History, popular images, comparative college guides
  - History, self images, to 1980
  - History, self images, 1981-
  - Homecoming-Parents Weekend
  - Housing, to 1989
  - Housing, 1990-
  - Humor, 19th century
  - Humor, 1900-1985
  - Humor, 1986-2000
  - Humor, 2001-
  - India, interests in, relations with
  - Jews, Jewish life at Wesleyan University
  - Key to the campus
  - Latinos
  - Lectures and addresses
  - Mace
  - Malcolm X Day, Feb. 21, 1969
  - Meetings and conferences
  - Methodism, ties with
  - Middle East issues
  - Missionaries
  - Mission and goals
  - Music and songs copyright
  - Music and songs, to 1950
  - Music and songs, 1950-
  - Muslims
  - Name, changing of
  - Native Americans
  - Newspaper readership program
  - Non-traditional students
  - Nudity
  - Open Mic Night
  - Parents Day
  - Parents
  - Planning
  - Poetry festival
  - Political attitudes
  - Political candidates and races
  - Pornography
  - Post-college careers
  - Pre-med
  - Protests, general, 1991-
  - Protests, 19th century
  - Protests, anti-nuclear
  - Protests, anti-war
  - Protests, campaign finance reform
  - Protests, financial aid
  - Protests, firebombing/racism, April 1990 events
  - Protests, firebombing/racism, May 1990 events
  - Protests, firebombing/racism, summer 1990 and aftermath
  - Protests, firebombing/racism, Kofi Taha trial
  - Protests, globalization
  - Protests, Independent Ivy
  - Protests, labor
  - Protests, police
  - Protests, racism
  - Protests, sexism
  - Protests, South African investments, 1977-1984
  - Protests, South African investments, 1985
  - Queer issues
  - Racism/Racial incidents
  - Religion, to 1960, chapel/assembly
  - Religion, to 1960, schedules, chapel assignments
  - Religion, general, 1961-
  - Science
  - Seal
  - September 11, 2001, terrorist attacks
  - Sexual assault
  - Socialism/Socialist Organizing Committee
  - Speech code, 1993-
  - Teacher education
  - Technology/communication systems
  - Tradition
  - Transportation
  - Videos/films
  - Wartime measures
  - Civil War
  - World War I
  - World War I, photos
  - World War II, general
  - World War II
  - World War II, directories and info booklets
  - World War II, religious services
  - World War II, S.S. Wesleyan Victory
  - Weshop
  - Wesleyan Challenge
  - Women/Feminism
  - Zonker Harris Day
- Administration/Administrative Units
  - Administration, general
  - Administration, retirements
  - Academic Affairs, Office of
  - Admissions, general
  - Admissions (Office), individuals
  - Admissions, policy
  - Affirmative Action, Office of
  - Archives
  - Audio-visual
  - Bookshop
  - Box Office
  - Broad Street Books
  - Career Resource Center
  - Career Planning Center Newsletter, ephemera
  - Center for Advanced Studies, 1959-1969
  - Center for Community Partnerships
  - Center for Continuing Studies
  - Center for the Arts
  - Center for the Humanities (CHUM)
  - Center for the Humanities, 1968-1979
  - Center for the Humanities, 1980-
  - Center for Prison Education
  - Chancellor, 1969-
  - Cinema Archives
  - College church
  - College store
  - Committees, Financial Planning
  - Communications, University
  - Community Service, Office of
  - Computing Center, users and facilities
  - Computer Institute (summer)
  - Controllers Office
  - Davison Art Center
  - Davison Art Center, Friends of, 1962-1979
  - Davison Art Center, Friends of, 1980-
  - Dean of the College/Deans Office
  - Deans, Academic, 1986-
  - Environmental Management Committee (EMC)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Office
  - Finance
  - Financial Aid
  - Freeman Center for East Asian Studies
  - Graduate Council
  - Graduate Student Services, Office of
  - Health Education Office
  - Health Service
  - Health Service, individuals
  - Health Service, reports
  - Human Resources
  - Information Technology Services (ITS)
  - International Studies Office, 1993-
  - Institute for Lifelong Learning
  - Institutional Research and Career Planning, reports
  - Landmarks Advisory Board
  - Language Lab
  - Library (Olin), 1831-1920
  - Library (Olin), 1920-1970
  - Library (Olin), 1971-
  - Library (Olin), exhibits
  - Library (Olin), Friends of
  - Library (Olin), funds, gifts, etc.
  - Library (Olin), history and recollections
  - Library (Olin): Check It Out, 1998-
  - Library (Olin), publications and handouts
  - Library (Olin), Science Library
  - Library (Olin), Special Collections & Archives
  - Ministry reports
  - Multicultural Affairs
  - Museum, general
  - Museum, mummy
  - Museum, particular objects, donors
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), Local 153
  - Physical Education
  - Physical Plant
  - Physical Plant, individuals
  - Provost's Office
  - Psychological Services
  - Public Safety
  - Publications, Office of
  - Registrar's Office
  - Residential Life, Office of
  - RIDE
  - SC & A Annual Reports
  - Secretarial-clerical forum, bulk 1975-1979
  - Secretarial-clerical strikes
  - Senate
  - Senate minutes and reports
  - Service Learning Center
  - Student Academic Resource Network (SARN)
  - Treasurer
  - Treasurers Office, individuals
  - University Coordinator
  - University Relations
  - Wesleyan Media Project
  - Wesleyan University Press, 1949-1965
  - Wesleyan University Press
  - Wesleyan University Press, misc. booklists and prospectuses
  - WesTel
  - WesWell
  - Women's Resource Center
  - Writing
- Admissions, Orientation, Parents, and Student Life
  - Admissions recruiting, 19th century
  - Admissions recruiting, 1900-1960
  - Admissions recruiting, 1960-1990
  - Admissions recruiting, 1990-2000
  - Admissions recruiting, 2000-
  - Expenses, self-help
  - Frosh, information for incoming
  - Orientation, to 1980
  - Orientation, from 1980-
  - Parents, information for
  - Parents Council, Parentline
  - Parents funds
  - Sons & Daughters Program
  - WesFest
  - Regulations
  - Seniors
  - Social life
  - Spring Fling
  - Student life, general
  - General, photos
  - Student exchanges and leaves
  - Student hi-jinks/pranks
  - Special needs
  - Tuition
  - WesLead
- Alumni: General, Organizations, and Fundraising
  - Admissions recruiting
  - Alumni commencement and reunion activities, luncheons and dinners
  - Alumni commencement and reunion activities, general
  - Alumni commencement and reunion activities, photos
  - Alumni commencement and reunion activities, programs, 1864-1959
  - Alumni commencement and reunion activities, programs, 1960-1995
  - Alumni commencement and reunion activities, programs, 1996-
  - Alumni commencement and reunion activities, trips and seminars
  - Distinguished Alumni Awards
  - Life-long learning
  - Miscellaneous
  - Alumni Record
  - Statistics, 1833-1965
  - Statistics, 1966-
  - Trustee elections
  - Alumni Association
  - Alumni clubs
  - Alumni clubs, photos
  - Alumni Council, general
  - Alumni Council, photos
  - Alumni Council material from A. B. Haley, class of 1907
  - Council meetings, 1927-1938
  - Council meetings, 1940-1954
  - Council reports, 1964-1974
  - Council reports, 1975-
  - Alumni education
  - Black Alumni Council
  - Committee of One Hundred, 1957
  - WESPAN
  - WESTAR
  - Alumni fundraising, general
  - Annual fund
  - Campaign for Liberal Learning, 1980s
  - Capital campaign, 1997
  - Davison Dinner, general
  - Davison Dinner, photos
  - Development campaign, 1952-1954
  - Development campaign, 1952-1954, reports and proposals
  - Development campaign, 1963-1971
  - Fifteenth Decade Fund
  - Alumni Fund, 1902-1955
  - Vanguard Fund
  - Wesleyan Alumni Fund, general
  - Wesleyan Alumni Fund, materials
  - Wesleyan Alumni Fund, reports
  - The Wesleyan Campaign
- Areas, Facilities, Landscaping
  - Andrus Field
  - Andrus Field, photos
  - Cemetery, Foss Hill
  - Cemetery, Foss Hill, photos
  - Class ivies
  - Denison Terrace
  - Denison Terrace, photos
  - Electrical plant
  - Facilities
  - Fauver Field
  - Fence, front campus
  - Flag pole, near South College
  - Foss Hill
  - Johnston Quadrangle
  - Kiosks/signs
  - Landscaping
  - Lighting
  - Parking
  - Perruccio Bench
  - Playing fields
  - Pump, behind North College
  - Sesquicentennial negatives
  - Sidewalks
  - Streets
  - Tishler Terrace
  - Tunnels
  - Wildlife Preserve (New Fairfield)
  - Woodframe houses
- Athletics
  - General
  - General, photos
  - General, tickets
  - History, Craig, 1987
  - Intramurals
  - Interscholastic Athletic Association
  - Non-organized sports
  - Schedules I, 1899-1950
  - Schedules II, 1950-1970
  - Schedules III, 1970-1980
  - Schedules IV, 1980-
  - Trainers
  - Women
  - Women, particular sports
  - Football, general
  - Football, schedules and press books
  - Football, action photos I, to 1940
  - Football, action photos II
  - Football, coaching I
  - Football, coaching II
  - Football, players I, photos
  - Football, players II, photos, to 1945
  - Football, players, III, photos, to 1940s
  - Football, players IV, photos, 1940s
  - Football, players V, photos, 1945-
  - Football, teams, photos, 1881-1889
  - Football, teams, photos, 1890-1900
  - Football, teams, photos, 1901-1906
  - Football, teams, photos, 1907-1920
  - Football, teams, photos, 1921-1939
  - Football, teams, photos, 1940-1950
  - Football, teams, photos, 1951
  - Football, tickets
  - General
  - Baseball, general
  - Baseball, ticketing, programs, and schedules I, to 1910
  - Baseball, ticketing, programs, and schedules II, 1910-
  - Baseball, players
  - Baseball, teams
  - Baseball, photos
  - Baseball, teams, photos I
  - Baseball, teams, photos II
  - Baseball, players, photos
  - Basketball, general
  - Basketball, general, photos
  - Basketball, programs I, to 1940
  - Basketball, programs II, 1940-
  - Basketball, players
  - Basketball, players, photos
  - Basketball, teams, photos
  - Bowling
  - Boxing, photos
  - Cheerleaders, photos
  - Crew, general
  - Crew, history
  - Crew, photos
  - Cricket
  - Fencing
  - Golf/Golf course
  - Gymnastics
  - Handball
  - Ice hockey
  - Ice hockey, photos
  - Lacrosse
  - Riding
  - Rugby
  - Soccer
  - Soccer, photos
  - Soccer, players, photos
  - Soccer, teams
  - Soccer, teams, photos
  - Softball
  - Squash
  - Swimming, general
  - Swimming, photos
  - Swimming, individuals
  - Swimming, individuals, photos
  - Swimming, teams
  - Swimming, teams, photos
  - Table tennis
  - Tennis
  - Track and cross country
  - Track and cross country, photos
  - Track and cross country, individuals
  - Track and cross country, teams
  - Track and cross country, teams, photos
  - Track and cross country, programs I
  - Track and cross country, programs II
  - Ultimate frisbee
  - Volleyball
  - Water polo
  - Wrestling, general
  - Wrestling, photos
- Buildings (General)
  - Ready Reference/General
  - Accessibility
  - Buildings and Ground in the Earliest Years
  - Costs (1913-1916)
  - Naming
- Buildings
  - Admissions (Reid Admission Center), 1997-
  - (Center for) Afro-American Studies (Malcolm X House, 343 High Street)
  - (Center for) African-American Studies (Malcolm X House, 343 High Street)Photos
  - Alumni Athletic Building (The Cage)
  - Alumni Athletic Building (The Cage), photos
  - Alumni and Development Office (255 High Street)
  - Alumni and Development Office (255 High Street), photos
  - Alumni House (284 High)
  - Alumni House (284 High)Photos
  - Alumni Office (291 Washington Terrace)
  - Anthropology Department Offices (281 High Street)
  - Anthropology Department Offices (281 High Street), photos
  - Armstrong House (356 Washington Street)
  - Armstrong House (356 Washington Street), photos
  - Bacon Field House
  - Boat House, old
  - Boat House, old, photos
  - Butterfield Colleges (Lawn Avenue)
  - Butterfield Colleges (Lawn Avenue), photos
  - Center for Film Studies
  - Center for the Arts I
  - Center for the Arts II
  - Center for the Arts, photos
  - Center for the Humanities
  - Center for the Humanities, photos
  - Chapel, Memorial, exterior
  - Chapel, Memorial, interior
  - Chapel, Memorial, organ
  - Chapel, Memorial, stained glass windows
  - Chapel, Memorial, stained glass windows, photos
  - Chapel, Memorial, photos
  - Christian Association Cabin (Westfield, Conn.)
  - Christian Association Cabin (Westfield, Conn.), photos
  - 200 Church Street
  - Clark Hall
  - Clark Hall, photos
  - College Hall (Old Boarding Hall)
  - Court Street Apartments
  - Davenport Campus Center
  - Davison Art Center I
  - Davison Art Center II
  - Davison Art Center I, photos
  - Davison Art Center II, photos
  - Davison Art Center III, photos
  - Davison Infirmary (Health Center)
  - Davison Infirmary (Health Center), photos
  - Downey House
  - Downey House, photos
  - East Hall Quail Roost
  - East Hall Quail Roast, photos
  - Emerson Boat House
  - English Department Office (285 Court Street)
  - English Department (285 Court Street), photos
  - Faculty Residences
  - Faculty Residences, photos
  - Fauver Field Residences
  - Fayerweather Gymnasium
  - Fayerweather Gymnasium II
  - Fayerweather Gymnasium, photos
  - Fayerweather Gymnasium Swimming Pool
  - Fayerweather Gymnasium Swimming Pool, photos
  - Fisk Hall
  - Fisk Hall, photos
  - Fisk Home (corner of High Street and Church Street)
  - Fisk Home (corner of High Street and Church Street), photos
  - Foss Hill Dormitories
  - Foss Hill Dormitories, photos
  - Foss House I
  - Foss House II
  - Foss House, photos
  - Freeman Athletic Center, 1986-1989
  - Freeman Athletic Center, 1989-
  - Freeman Athletic Center, 1986-1989, photos
  - Freeman Center for East Asian Studies
  - Graduate Summer School/Graduate Liberal Arts Program (287 High Street)
  - Gymnasium, old, 1864-1897
  - Gymnasium, old, photos
  - Hall Laboratory
  - Hall Laboratory, photos
  - Harrison Hall
  - Harrison Hall, photos
  - Harrington Lodge (North Woodstock, NH)
  - Harrington Lodge (North Woodstock, NH), photos
  - Hi Rise/Lo Rise
  - 208 High Street, Public Safety
  - 330 High Street
  - Hockey Rink
  - Horgan House
  - Housing Office (190 High Street)
  - Housing Office (190 High Street), photos
  - Judd Hall
  - Judd Hall I, photos
  - Judd Hall II, photos
  - Judd Hall Museum, photos
  - Laboratory, old
  - Laboratory, old, photos
  - Mansfield Freeman Center for East Asian Studies
  - McConaughy Dining Hall
  - McConaughy Dining Hall, photos
  - Museum (proposed)
  - Nicholson (Foss Hill Dormitory)
  - Ninety-Two ('92) Theatre (Rich Hall) I
  - Ninety-Two ('92) Theatre (Rich Hall) II
  - Ninety-Two ('92) Theatre (Rich Hall), 1870-1928, photos
  - Ninety-Two ('92) Theatre (Rich Hall), 1930-, photos
  - North College I, to March 1906
  - North College, 1906 fire
  - North College II, rebuilt 1907
  - North College I, to 1906, photos
  - North College Ia, to 1906, photos
  - North College II, rebuilt 1907, photos
  - North College, interior
  - Observatory Hall
  - Observatory Hall, photos
  - Olin Library I, 1914-1939
  - Olin Library I, exterior, photos
  - Olin Library II, 1940-1985
  - Olin Library II, interior, photos
  - Olin Library III, 1986-
  - Olin Library III, interior, photos
  - Olin Library 1986 Architecture, Citations
  - Olin Library 9/24/1983 Cornerstone Ceremony
  - Olin Library Lobby
  - Olin Library 9/13/1986 Rededication Ceremony
  - Olin Library 1979-1983 Renovation Planning
  - Olin Library Information Commons
  - Olin Library Tapestries
  - Outing Club Cabin
  - Outing Club CabinPhotos
  - 227 Pine Street Women of Color House
  - Power House, New
  - Power House, Old
  - Power House, Old--Photos
  - Presidents House
  - Presidents HousePhotos
  - Public Affairs Center
  - Public Affairs CenterPhotos
  - Russell House I
  - Russell House II
  - Russell House II - Photos
  - Science Center I
  - Science Center II
  - Science Center III
  - Science Center - photos
  - St Clements (Estate in Portland)
  - Scott Laboratory
  - Scott LaboratoryPhotos
  - Shanklin Laboratory
  - Shanklin LaboratoryPhotos
  - Shanklin (5)
  - South College I
  - South College Photos I
  - South College Photos II
  - South College Bells I
  - South College Bells II
  - Squash Courts Building
  - Squash Courts BuildingPhotos
  - Student Center (Proposed)
  - Usdan University Center
  - Van Vleck Observatory I
  - Van Vleck Observatory II
  - Van Vleck Observatory Photos
  - Veterans Village
  - Wasch Center for Retired Faculty
  - 356 Washington Street (Acheson-Armstrong House)
  - (Governor) Weeks House
  - Weeks HousePhotos
  - West College
  - Williams Street Housing
  - Woodrow Wilson House
  - Woodrow Wilson HousePhotos
  - Zelnick Pavilion
  - Zilkha Gallery
- Campus
  - Campus planning
  - Representations
  - RepresentationsOrr, Louis, Etchings (1928)
  - RepresentationsOrr, Louis, Etchings (1928)Photos
  - RepresentationsPlates, Wesleyan Centennial & Other
  - Maps
  - Campus I
  - Campus II (1879)
  - Campus I, 1851-1879Photos
  - Campus II, 1879Photos
  - Campus III, 1880-1889Photos
  - Campus IV, 1890-1892Photos
  - Campus V, 1892-1900Photos
  - Campus VI, 1900-1909Photos
  - Campus VII, 1910-1930Photos
  - Campus VIII, 1933-1947Photos, undated
  - Campus IX Photos 1947-
  - Presidents Christmas [Holiday] Cards
  - College Row (Brownstone Row)
  - College Row (Brownstone Row) IPhotos
  - College Row (Brownstone Row) IIPhotos
- Colleges
  - College Plan I, 1957-59
  - College Plan II, 1960-62
  - East and West Colleges
- Courses
  - Courses, 19th century
  - Courses, 1901-1955
  - Grade inflation
  - Courses, over-enrollment
  - Courses, pre-registration
- Courses, particular
  - Combined Plan in Engineering Wesleyan/Columbia, 1951-
  - Fundamentals of Student Life, 1917-1918
  - Humanities Workshops, 1943-1968
  - Intensive Language Program (WILP)
  - January Term, 1972-1974
  - Radical Studies, 1970
  - Summer school of Chemistry and Biology, 1902
  - Science Center Summer Program, 1962
- Curriculum, general
  - Curriculum to 1955
  - Curriculum, Dunn Report (1955)
  - Curriculum, 1970-
  - Curriculum, multiculturalism, 1990- (see also: Protests, racism)
  - University Plan, 1992
- Curriculum, frosh
  - Curriculum, 1991-
  - Experimental curriculum, 1952-54
  - General education and the freshman year, 1976-83
  - Humanities program
  - Freshman integrated program, 1954-1989
  - University courses, 1977-84
- Divisions and Departments
  - Division I
  - Division II
  - Division III
  - Afro-American Studies, Center for
  - African-American Studies Program
  - American Studies
  - Anthropology
  - Archaeology
  - Art Laboratory - Print Shop
  - Art Programs
  - Asian Languages and Literatures
  - Astronomy
  - Astronomy - Photos
  - Biology
  - Biology - Photos
  - Center for the Americas
  - Chemistry, 1832-1968
  - Chemistry, 1968-
  - Chemistry - Atwater Fund
  - Chemistry - Leermakers Symposium
  - Chemistry - Photos
  - Classics
  - Cognitive Science
  - College of Letters
  - College of Social Studies
  - Dance
  - Earth & Environmental Science
  - East Asian Studies
  - Economics
  - Educational Studies Program
  - English
  - English - Writing Workshop
  - Ethnic Studies Program
  - Film Studies
  - Geology
  - German
  - Government
  - Hebrew
  - History
  - History & Theory - Reports
  - Jewish Studies
  - Latin American Studies
  - Mathematics
  - Mathematics - Ph.D. Program
  - Medieval Studies
  - Molecular Biology and Biochemistry
  - Music
  - Music - Ethnomusicology
  - Music - Individuals
  - Neuroscience and Behavior
  - Oral English
  - Philosophy
  - Physical Education
  - Physics
  - PIMMS
  - Psychology
  - Psychology - Ph.D. Program
  - Public Affairs Center
  - Public Affairs Center - Reports
  - Queer Studies
  - Religion